Clayton Curry

me@claycurry.com || +1 (405) 301-1055

Systems Design ∩ Information Technology ∩ Software Engineering

Summary

I bring 5 years of computer programming experience yielding a diverse portfolio of projects, professional achievements, and personal goals. Before obtaining my B.S. in Computer Science, I held two positions in OU IT where I was recruited by the director of my school to help facilitate access to high-performance computing infrastructure, administer open-source software, and design software tests on behalf of several research projects conducting research with the Department of Defense. This position offered 2 years of experience developing various new features to modernize legacy software.

At this point in my craft, I collect hours coding like a civil pilot collects flight hours before becoming an airline pilot. My biggest motivation to keep leveling up is the understanding that what's difficult for me now was likely difficult for someone else too. Leveling up at means giving back to make it easier for others to do the same. For this reason, I am particularly fond of building tools for supporting other developers.

Relevant Experience

Store Assistant | Starbucks June 2024 - Current 40 Hours / Week

- Provided personalized customer service, remembering regular customers' orders and preferences.
- Managed cash register operations, including handling cash and managing account balances
- Maintained a clean and organized store environment, following company standards for sanitation and food safety.
- Proactively identify and remove obstacles before the need arises

Pro Desk Assistant | The Home Depot June 2023 – October 2023 30 Hours / Week

> Monitored inventory stock and coordinated with multiple suppliers to ensure availability of highdemand items for approximately 30 private contractors and prevent inventory shortages

Machine Learning Research Assistant | University of Oklahoma Nov 2021 – Jan 2023 20 - 40 Hours / Week

 Implemented SQL tables and web scraping software to simultaneously poll real-time aircraft transponder (ADSB) messages from more than 2000 aircraft flying in the continental United States

- (source: github.com/clay-curry/Flight-Transponder-Dataset) broadcasted simultaneously and indefinitely
- Queried additional supporting data from primary and secondary sources, particularly government sources and statistics, followed by cleaning, interpreting, and merging with existing data sources
- Provided daily Linux infrastructure support such as in provisioning, installation, configuration, operation, and maintenance of system software databases to ensure compliance with security protocols and departmental technical strategy
- Worked with management to prioritize access to the most relevant software libraries on behalf of 10 United States Air Force civilian research engineers investigating neural network-based machine learning algorithms in airspace monitoring for Airborne Early Warning & Control Systems
- Methodically documented new technical procedures to ensure recurring problems are easily resolved if not proactively avoided

Linux System Administrator | OU Department of Physics and Astronomy February 2021 – Nov 2021

20 Hours / Week

- Provided system-facing and people-facing IT support in Red Hat Enterprise Linux to more than 250 end users (graduate students, teaching faculty, and staff)
- Managed SQL based mailing lists, email addresses, domain names, software packages, software licenses, and network logs
- Documented any evolving procedures, software upgrades, software requirements, and reporting tools (Grafana)
- Oversaw the migration of the department's website server IT platform from on-premises to secure, interoperable AWS services, saving months of labor on project completion with web-scraping (source: github.com/clay-curry/Crawler)
- Deployed numerous Bash scripts for network-wide intrusion-detection and remote device management

Basketball Referee | Independent Contractor Dec 2015 – Feb 2021

12 Hours / Week

- Provided part-time refereeing on behalf of multiple school districts and local basketball leagues
- Learned teamwork, pressure management, people management, and coaching others as an OSSAA-certified basketball referee for school-sanctioned basketball games from kindergarten to high school varsity levels

Awards

- scraping course evaluation data in from PDF documents for analysis in R
- creating daemons for tracking network availability in Red Hat Enterprise Linux
- scraping (> 100 gb / day) crowd-sourced air traffic data to characterize trajectories using a learning algorithm

- creating a dashboard for the above daemon in the MUI design language to facilitate system visual analytics

Awards

Oklahoma Academic Scholar | Oklahoma State Regents for Higher Education

- Earned a merit-based full-ride scholarship to the university of Oklahoma scoring in the 99.5 percentile on the college-readiness ACT standardized test
- subsection assessments included perfect score in mathematics (36/36) and near-perfect in science (35/36)

Education

Choctaw High School, Oklahoma Academic Scholar

August 2012 - May 2017

University of Oklahoma, B.S. Computer Science, Minor: Mathematics

Aug 2017 – December 2023

NVIDIA Fundamentals of Deep Learning, Certification

June 2023

StanfordOnline STATSX0001: Statistical Learning Certification

June 2024